[{"stepName": "Identify Motion of objects", "stepNumber": 1, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "How many moving objects are present?", "options": [3, 1, 0, 2], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "motion", "threejssubstep": 0, "threejssubsubstep": 0, "show1": [""], "show2": [""], "showfc": [], "type": "basic", "showfcheading": []}]}, {"stepName": "Write FBD equation for each Moving block", "stepNumber": 2, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2081-N\u2082+20=0", "+N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "-N\u2081-N\u2082+20=0", "-N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -300, "show1": [], "show2": ["+N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["N\u2081: Normal between red block and ceiling/ground 1yellow block and red blockblue block and yellow block", "N\u2081: Normal between ", "N\u2081: Normal between "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is the direction of normal reaction on block 1 due to c1?", "options": ["N1 perpendicular up", "N1 perpendicular down"], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": [], "show2": [], "type": "advance", "answer": 0, "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"]}, {"question": "What is the direction of normal reaction on block 1 due to b2?", "options": ["N2 perpendicular up", "N2 perpendicular down"], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": [], "show2": [], "type": "advance", "answer": 1, "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N1, ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"]}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for red block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": [], "show2": [], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "answer": 0}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2081-N\u2082+20=0", "+N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "-N\u2081-N\u2082+20=0", "-N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": [], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N1, ", "Downward Forces: N2, 20", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0", "+N\u2082-N\u2083+10=0", "-N\u2082-N\u2083+10=0", "-N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -300, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "+N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["N\u2081: Normal between red block and ceiling/ground 1yellow block and red blockblue block and yellow block", "N\u2081: Normal between ", "N\u2081: Normal between "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is the direction of normal reaction on block 2 due to b1?", "options": ["N2 perpendicular up", "N2 perpendicular down"], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "type": "advance", "answer": 0, "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"]}, {"question": "What is the direction of normal reaction on block 2 due to b3?", "options": ["N3 perpendicular up", "N3 perpendicular down"], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "type": "advance", "answer": 1, "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N2, ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"]}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for yellow block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "answer": 0}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0", "+N\u2082-N\u2083+10=0", "-N\u2082-N\u2083+10=0", "-N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N2, ", "Downward Forces: N3, 10", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of blue block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2083+30=0", "-N\u2083+30=0", "+N\u2083-30=0", "-N\u2083-30=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": -300, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0", "+N\u2083-30=0"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["N\u2081: Normal between red block and ceiling/ground 1yellow block and red blockblue block and yellow block", "N\u2081: Normal between ", "N\u2081: Normal between "], "showfcheading": ["Blue block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is the direction of normal reaction on block 3 due to b2?", "options": ["N3 perpendicular up", "N3 perpendicular down"], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0"], "type": "advance", "answer": 0, "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Blue block"]}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for blue block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0"], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Blue block"], "answer": 0}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of blue block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2083+30=0", "-N\u2083+30=0", "+N\u2083-30=0", "-N\u2083-30=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0"], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N3, ", "Downward Forces: 30", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Blue block"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0", "Blue block: +N\u2083-30=0"]}]}, {"stepName": "Constraint Equations", "stepNumber": 3, "stepQuestions": []}, {"stepName": "Final Answers", "stepNumber": 4, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "What are the final accelerations, tensions and normal reactions?", "options": ["N\u2081= 60.0, N\u2082= 40.0, N\u2083= 30.0", "N\u2081= -40.0, N\u2082= -30.0, N\u2083= -60.0", "N\u2081= -60.0, N\u2082= -30.0, N\u2083= -40.0", "N\u2081= -40.0, N\u2082= -30.0, N\u2083= -60.0"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "finalanswer", "threejssubstep": 0, "threejssubsubstep": 0, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0", "Blue block: +N\u2083-30=0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": [], "tobeshown": 1, "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-N\u2083-10=0", "Blue block: +N\u2083-30=0", "Final Answers: N\u2081= 60.0, N\u2082= 40.0, N\u2083= 30.0"]}]}]